[
    {
        "question": "Accra is the capital of which African country?",
        "answer": "Ghana"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ghana is located along which gulf?",
        "answer": "Gulf of Guinea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ocean does Ghana have water access to?",
        "answer": "Atlantic"
    },
    {
        "question": "Wisconsin has a shoreline along which two Great Lakes?",
        "answer": "Superior and Michigan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to Wind Cave?",
        "answer": "South Dakota"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state shares a border with the Canadian province of New Brunswick?",
        "answer": "Maine"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the world`s oldest desert?",
        "answer": "Namibia Desert"
    },
    {
        "question": "What U.S. city has an airport named after a President and First Lady?",
        "answer": "Little Rock, Arkansas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where are the Baalbek Roman ruins located?",
        "answer": "Lebanon"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many states does Mexico have?",
        "answer": "31"
    },
    {
        "question": "What constellation appears on the Alaskan flag?",
        "answer": "Ursa Major"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the tallest mosque in the world?",
        "answer": "Morocco"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country owns the island of Corfu?",
        "answer": "Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "What South American cities inhabitants are called `portenos`?",
        "answer": "Buenos Aires"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest country wholly within Europe?",
        "answer": "France"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is Moscow`s famed opera house?",
        "answer": "The Bolshoi Theatre"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Libya on the East?",
        "answer": "Egypt"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what Australian state would you find Port Pirie?",
        "answer": "South Australia"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state is Stone Mountain?",
        "answer": "Georgia"
    },
    {
        "question": "On which river is Warsaw to be found?",
        "answer": "Vistula"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Kung San people live in what area of Africa?",
        "answer": "Kalahari Desert in Botswana"
    },
    {
        "question": "What part of the world did the Vikings come from?",
        "answer": "Scandinavia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the coldest permanently inhabited town on Earth?",
        "answer": "Oymyakon, Russia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Belhaven Bridge, nicknamed the `Bridge to Nowhere`, is located in which country?",
        "answer": "Scotland -- It crosses Biel Water, a large stream that flows through the small village of Biel, and empties into the North Sea."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the oldest building in New York City?",
        "answer": "The Wyckoff House -- AKA the Wyckoff Farm, it a humble Dutch structure that dates all the way back to 1652!"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the most isolated town in the contiguous U.S. states?",
        "answer": "Glasgow, Montana -- The nearest city in any direction is a 4.5-hour drive away."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which animal is pictured on the Canadian $2 coin?",
        "answer": "Polar bear"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where can you climb the world`s longest staircase.",
        "answer": "Switzerland -- It takes 11,674 steps to climb the two-mile-long staircase winding up the side of Mount Niesen."
    },
    {
        "question": "In which European country is the Drin the longest river?",
        "answer": "Albania -- 175 miles flow through Albania, making the Drin the longest river in the country."
    },
    {
        "question": "From whom did the US buy the Virgin Islands?",
        "answer": "Denmark"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where was milk chocolate invented?",
        "answer": "Switzerland -- In the 1876, Daniel Peter developed a smoother chocolate by adding dried milk powder to the mixture."
    },
    {
        "question": "What colors are featured on the Chinese flag?",
        "answer": "Red and yellow."
    },
    {
        "question": "Who became president of Brazil in 2019?",
        "answer": "Jair Bolsonaro"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the driest, non-polar desert on Earth?",
        "answer": "Atacama Desert"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state has the nickname `The Palmetto State`?",
        "answer": "South Carolina"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the southern most city in the contiguous U.S.?",
        "answer": "Key West"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two countries border the Dead Sea?",
        "answer": "Israel and Jordan"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what direction does the Nile River flow?",
        "answer": "North"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country`s capital is Montevideo?",
        "answer": "Uruguay"
    },
    {
        "question": "Moroni is the capital of which African country?",
        "answer": "Comoros"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the African country of Comoros?",
        "answer": "Moroni"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which continent is the country Comoros located in?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "The country Comoros is part of which continent?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ocean surrounds the Union of the Comoros?",
        "answer": "Indian Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Union of the Comoros is located in which ocean?",
        "answer": "Indian Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "Brisbane is the capital of which Australian state?",
        "answer": "Queensland"
    },
    {
        "question": "The town of Pisa lies in which Italian region?",
        "answer": "Tuscany"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Rijksmuseum is located in what European city?",
        "answer": "Amsterdam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to Guadalupe Mountains National Park?",
        "answer": "Texas"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Australian state surrounds the city of Canberra?",
        "answer": "New South Wales"
    }
]